{
  "version": 2.0,
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "1. A Temperature Control System is known as:",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Process Control System",
        "b": "Servomechanism",
        "c": "Cascade Control System",
        "d": "None of The above"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "a",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "2. The time constant of a servo control system can be decreased by",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Decreasing the inertia of the system",
        "b": "Decreasing the damping of the system",
        "c": "Both of the above",
        "d": "None of the above"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "3. Identify the transducer not used for the measurement of temperature.",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Thermocouple",
        "b": "RVDT",
        "c": "RTD",
        "d": "Pyrometer"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "4. RTD and Thermistors are _____ transducers.",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Passive and analog",
        "b": "Passive and digital",
        "c": "Active and digital",
        "d": "Active and analog"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "a",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "5. The function of the proportional mode is to ____________?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Provide Gain",
        "b": "Eliminate Offsets",
        "c": "To speed up the response and minimize the overshoot",
        "d": "All of the above"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "a",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
	{
      "question": "6. The function of the proportional plus integral mode is to ____________?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Provide Gain",
        "b": "Eliminate Offsets",
        "c": "To speed up the response and minimize the overshoot",
        "d": "All of the above"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },	
	
	{
      "question": "7. Gain and proportional bands are",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Two different control modes",
        "b": "Reciprocally related",
        "c": "Adjusted independently of one another",
        "d": "Controller functions calibrated in time units"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
	
	{
      "question": "8. The term reset control refers to ____ control",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Derivative",
        "b": "Integral",
        "c": "Proportional",
        "d": "None of the above"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
	
	
	{
      "question": "9. Which of the following is an active transducer ?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Strain gauge",
        "b": "Thermistor",
        "c": "LVDT",
        "d": "Thermocouple"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "d",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
	
	{
      "question": "10. In which one of the following temperature sensors, the excitation or power is needed?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Thermocouple",
        "b": "Semiconductor temperature sensor",
        "c": "Thermistor",
        "d": "None of the above"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    }
	
  ]
}

